Friends, we were at
Ca and Lena's release party and of
course I took you along again.
The location was decorated so incredibly
beautifully.  You could
take lots of pictures here.  And here are
the perfumes.  Oh my God.  And they
smell incredibly good.  You won't believe it
.  I can't even
say which of the two scents is my favorite
, because they both smell so incredibly good
.  At 6 pm, Kamena and Sinan
came down the stairs and then gave a
speech, guys.  And it was so cute.
I almost started crying along with them because
they both started crying.  It
was just so incredibly cute, really.
If they had continued crying, I would have
really started to
cry myself.  There was, by the way, such delicious
food.  The mini burgers were especially
delicious, and oh my
god, you could even have your
perfume engraved on them.  I then had
Priscilla engraved because I
somehow like the name more than Stephanie.   That
's my middle name.  We got some more
drinks and then sat down
and guys, this video, it
looks so iconic.  I don't know.  There was
even a Rorka Kamata stand run by
Nona.  Nuna was just there too, guys.
And this Strawberry Match tastes so
amazing, guys.  You don't get it.  Of course,
I also had to taste-test the nine matchers with mango
.  Guys, it
tasted so delicious, even though I do
n't usually like mango that much.  In the
end, everyone got a goodie
bag, guys.  And if you want to know
what was inside, feel free to write it
in the comments and then
I'll gladly make it into a video.